Guide to the Yasser Alwan Collection AD.MC.002
New York University Abu Dhabi Library
- Series II: Egypt, 1895-1971; 585 (Box 1-7)
  - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series, 1412
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - An elephant in a zoo raising its trunk. 6.1 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid899; 1332; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Elephants; Photographic Prints; Zoos; Animals; Egypt
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Houseboats along the banks of the Nile River. 6.0 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid900; 1333; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Nile River; Photographic Prints; Boats/Ships; Egypt; Rivers; Buildings
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Pelicans. 6.1 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid901; 1334; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Animals; Gelatin Silver Prints; Birds; Photographic Prints; Nile River; Egypt
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A marching band in uniform walking down the street. 6.1 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid902; 1335; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Horses; Egypt; Buildings; Musical Instruments; Musicians; Gelatin Silver Prints; Animals; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Uniforms; Architecture; Street Lamps; Marching Band; Parades/Processions; Men; Fezes/Tarbouches; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men in tarbouches and suits sitting in front of a high wall. 5.8 x 5.7 cm, 1945; cuid903; 1336; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Men; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Fezes/Tarbouches; Choubra/Shubra, Egypt; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men walking on the beach. 6.2 x 6.1 cm, 1937; cuid904; 1337; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Buildings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Newspapers/Magazines; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Beaches; Arabic Writing; Fezes/Tarbouches; Alexandria, Egypt; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A baby in a pram. 6.0 x 5.8 cm, 1933; cuid905; 1338; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Children; Arabic Writing; Ismailia, Egypt
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A dog named Beeki sitting on a carpet. 6.4 x 6.1 cm, 1944; cuid906; 1339; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 2)
      Arabic Writing; Animals; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Dogs
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A couple standing on a pier over water. 9.8 x 7.0 cm, Undated; cuid907; 1340; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Photographic Prints; Boats/Ships; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Egypt; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A large group of boys with some men. 5.9 x 8.8 cm, 31st of October,1934; cuid908; 1341; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Boys; Children; Egypt; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - The Head of the Colussus of Rameses II, at the Thebian Necropolis. 10.9 x 6.9 cm, 27 February 1926; cuid909; 1342; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Arabic Writing; Statues/Sculptures; Gelatin Silver Prints; Luxor, Egypt; Thebes, Egypt; Men; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two boys boxing. 6.1 x 9.2 cm, Undated; cuid910; 1343; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Children; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sports; Boys; Photographic Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man in a tarbouche standing in the garden. 11.5 x 8.0 cm, 1933; cuid911; 1344; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Gardens; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Fezes/Tarbouches; Ismailia, Egypt; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young man wearing a tarbouche and a bow tie, rubber stamps on image. 5.9 x 4.8 cm, 1938; cuid912; 1345; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Photographic Prints; Bow Ties; Men; Arabic Writing; Fezes/Tarbouches; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Postal Stamps; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Children on the beach playing with sand. 6.5 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid913; 1346; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Beaches; Children; Boys; Egypt; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A baby being held by an adult. 6.5 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid914; 1347; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Children; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group on a balcony, over looking the sea (linked ref1002). 6.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid915; 1348; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Men; Telephones; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Seas; Photographic Prints; Women; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men and a woman standing on a balcony, near the beach (linked ref942). 6.4 x 8.9 cm, Undated; cuid916; 1408; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 9)
      Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Group Portraits; Seas
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Five children in a field. 6.5 x 9.4 cm, Undated; cuid917; 1349; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 3)
      Horses; Animals; Girls; Countryside/Rural; Boys; Group Portraits; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men sitting in chairs, listening to a speech celebrating prophet Mohamed's birth at Al Abbassiya secondary school (linked ref945). 6.4 x 9.0 cm, 1949; cuid918; 1350; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Speeches; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Audiences/Spectators; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fezes/Tarbouches; Men; Arabic Writing; Cairo, Egypt; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group portrait of a man and a woman with six children. 9.0 x 6.2 cm, 1949; cuid919; 1351; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Men; Arabic Writing; Alexandria, Egypt; Group Portraits; Children; Boys; Girls; Women; Fezes/Tarbouches
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A family group pose on a rooftop. 6.1 x 8.5 cm, Undated; cuid920; 1352; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photographic Prints; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Women; Men; Children; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Three girls wearing matching outfits stnd beside a man and an ox. 6.4 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid921; 1353; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Animals; Cattle/Cows; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Girls; Gelatin Silver Prints; Countryside/Rural; Buildings; Group Portraits; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men sitting in cafe in front of Cinema Empire with a large banner for the film Monsieur Albert. 5.9 x 8.4 cm, Circa 1932; cuid922; 1354; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Cinema; Egypt; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Bicycles/Tricycles; Men; Restaurants/bars; Actors; Gelatin Silver Prints; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men and women in a park 6.2 x 8.7 cm, 1962; cuid923; 1355; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Egypt; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Parks; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A girl holding a brush. 9.6 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid924; 1356; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Egypt; Buildings; Individual Portraits; Children; Photographic Prints; Girls; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman in a strapless dress, looking off camera. 8.6 x 5.6 cm, Undated; cuid925; 1357; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Photographic Prints; Women; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men in a photo booth, one in military uniform. 4.5 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid926; 1358; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Photo Booth; Men; Arabic Writing; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Medals/Insignia; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young woman on the telephone in a photo booth. 4.9 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid927; 1359; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 4)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Telephones; Individual Portraits; Jewelry; Women
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two women embracing in a photo booth. 4.5 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid928; 1360; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Women; Group Portraits; Jewelry
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman wearing a beret, posing in a photo booth. 4.7 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid929; 1361; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Jewelry; Hats; Girls; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Women; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of women and girls with musical instruments. 6.2 x 8.8 cm, Undated; cuid930; 1362; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Pianos; Girls; Women; Musical Instruments; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Oud; Group Portraits; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young woman in a white shirt and dark vest. 8.0 x 5.0 cm, 1932; cuid931; 1363; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Women
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A girl in a school uniform. 8.2 x 5.2 cm, Undated; cuid932; 1364; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Uniforms; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Girls; Jewelry; Students; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman seated on a sofa with a full face veil. 9.9 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid933; 1365; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Furnishings; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Head Covers/Veils; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two women in the garden. 11.0 x 6.4 cm, Undated; cuid934; 1366; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Gardens; Photographic Prints; Head Covers/Veils; Women; Egypt; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A boy leaning on a table. 8.9 x 6.8 cm, Undated; cuid935; 1367; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Photographic Prints; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Fezes/Tarbouches; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Egypt; Furnishings
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman leaning on a piece of furniture. 11.2 x 6.8 cm, Undated; cuid936; 1368; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Egypt; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man sitting in front of a large plant. 8.9 x 6.3 cm, Undated; cuid937; 1369; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 5)
      Egypt; Individual Portraits; Parks; Photographic Prints; Gardens; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A young man standing in front of two cannons. 6.4 x 8.8 cm, 1931; cuid938; 1370; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Egypt; Buildings; Individual Portraits; English Writing; Cannons; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Weapons
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man sitting with crossed legs in a garden. 8.7 x 6.0 cm, 7 September 1935; cuid939; 1371; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Men; Fezes/Tarbouches; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Gardens; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A cyclist riding a bicycle. 9.0 x 6.4 cm, 15 October 1933; cuid940; 1372; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Bicycles/Tricycles; Men; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Sports
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man reaching the top of the one of the Pyramids, possibly the Pyramid of Khafre. 9.0 x 5.9 cm, Undated; cuid941; 1373; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Men; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Individual Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men and boys standing in front of a building. 6.3 x 8.8 cm, 28th October 1934; cuid942; 1374; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Fezes/Tarbouches; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Group Portraits; Men; Boys; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of young men outside a large complex. 6.5 x 9.1 cm, 21st of March 1937; cuid943; 1375; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Boys; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Children; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group with some officials walking through a rural area. 6.8 x 11.3 cm, 22 October 1933; cuid944; 1376; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Countryside/Rural; Oases; Turbans; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Fezes/Tarbouches; Regional/National Dress; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Arabic Writing; Men; Aswan, Egypt; Boys; Children; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A man and woman sitting on deck chairs on the beach. 7.4 x 11.6 cm, Undated; cuid945; 1377; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Women; Photographic Prints; Beaches; Egypt; Men
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Five men on a hill overlooking the Nile. 8.5 x 11.2 cm, 11 November 1926; cuid946; 1378; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Countryside/Rural; Nile River; Egypt; Photographic Prints; Deserts; Men; Arabic Writing; Giza, Egypt; Pyramids; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men standing next to a palm tree. 8.6 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid947; 1379; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 6)
      Photographic Prints; Oases; Outdoors; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Regional/National Dress; Egypt; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two men playing ping-pong/table tennis on a terrace. Same man from ref1032. 6.5 x 10.4 cm, 17 February 1937; cuid948; 1380; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Photographic Prints; Sports; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; French Writing; Egypt; Architecture; Buildings
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Four men in tarbouches, sitting on wicker chairs on a terrace. 5.9 x 5.9 cm, Undated; cuid949; 1381; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Fezes/Tarbouches; Men; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Buildings; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group in a small boat on the Nile. 8.9 x 6.2 cm, Undated; cuid950; 1382; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Women; Men; Boats/Ships; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Nile River; Egypt; Children
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - An athlete throwing a discus. 9.2 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid951; 1383; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Buildings; Photographic Prints; Audiences/Spectators; Men; Sports; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Men wearing party hats. 8.3 x 5..9 cm, UNdated; cuid952; 1384; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Egypt; Waiters; Books; Group Portraits; Hats; Parties; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Photographic Prints
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Two boys in bathing suits, standing in front of a building. 8.9 x 6.0 cm, Undated; cuid953; 1385; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Boys; Egypt; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Group Portraits
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of men in lab coats, in a room with a painted stucco wall in the background (linked ref1036). 9.4 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid954; 1386; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Egypt; Uniforms; Photographic Prints; Lab Coats; Group Portraits; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints; Buildings; Frescoes
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A group of men, some in lab coats standing in front of some frescoes (linked ref980). 9.4 x 6.5 cm, Undated; cuid955; 1442; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 13)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Egypt; Frescoes; Group Portraits; Architecture; Buildings; Facial Hair
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - Four women in front of the Sphynx and the Pyramids of Giza. 8.6 x 5.8 cm, 25 January 1930; cuid956; 1387; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Giza, Egypt; Women; Photographic Prints; The Great Sphinx of Giza; Pyramids; French Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - The interior of the Sforzesco Castle in Milan, Italy. 6.6 x 9.4 cm, 15 September 1934; cuid957; 1388; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Architecture; Statues/Sculptures; French Writing; Milan, Italy; Forts/Castles; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Buildings
    - Ahmed Wali Al Din Series - A woman at the beach (same location as ref989). 4.0 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid958; 1389; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 7)
      Photographic Prints; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Women; Seas; Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Individual Portraits; Children; Boys; Water
  - Curly-Haired Woman Series, 1413
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman holding a veil over her face in a photo booth (same woman as ref987). 4.8 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid959; 1390; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photo Booth; Costumes; Head Covers/Veils; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Women; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - The woman from ref984 when she was a child. 6.1 x 4.1 cm, Undated; cuid960; 1391; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Girls; Egypt; Photo Booth; Individual Portraits; Children
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A man wearing a tarbouche, looking off camera. 4.6 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid961; 1392; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Fezes/Tarbouches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photo Booth; Men; Photographic Prints
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A young woman, posing with a white veil over her head (same woman as ref984). 4.3 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid962; 1393; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Individual Portraits; Costumes; Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Head Covers/Veils; Women
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman walking on the sidewalk, a building named 'Victoria House' is in the background.4.2 x 3.6 cm, Undated; cuid963; 1394; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photographic Prints; Cars/Trucks; Streets/Roads; Women; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Egypt; Signs/Signposts; Architecture; Buildings; Street Lamps; Transportation
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman on the pier by the beach (same location as ref983). 4.1 x 3.5 cm, Undated; cuid964; 1395; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Women; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Beaches; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Seas; Individual Portraits
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A group sitting under a parasol at the beach. 4.0 x 3.6 cm, Undated; cuid965; 1396; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Group Portraits; Women; Men; Beaches; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Umbrellas/Parasols
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A woman posing on the dock. 4.0 x 3.7 cm, Undated; cuid966; 1397; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Docks/Piers/Jetties; Women; Egypt
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A young woman looking off camera. 4.7 x 3.8 cm, 1952; cuid967; 1398; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Women; Arabic Writing
    - Curly-Haired Woman Series - A young woman, posing with her hands under her chin. 4.5 x 3.8 cm, Undated; cuid968; 1399; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 8)
      Photographic Prints; Photo Booth; Women; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt
  - Mansour Beih Series, 1414
    - Mansour Beih Series - Six men having a picnic (same handwriting on reverse as ref1082). 7.2 x 11.4 cm, Undated; cuid1053; 1487; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Food; Parks; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Men; Picnic; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Alcohol; Arabic Writing; Drinks/Beverages
    - Mansour Beih Series - Notre Dame Cathedral of Paris, France (same handwriting on reverse as ref1081). 7.2 x 11.5 cm, Undated; cuid1054; 1488; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Buildings; Notre Dame de Paris; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Churches; Paris, France; Arabic Writing; Religious Sites
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man wearing leather gloves, holding a hat. 11.1 x 6.7 cm, 31 May 1927; cuid1055; 1489; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Rivers; Men; Paris, France; Photographic Prints; French Writing; Handkerchiefs /Pocket Squares
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man wearing a dark coat and bowler hat on a bridge (linked ref1085, ref1086, ref1087 and ref1090). 11.0 x 8.4 cm, 22-1-1926; cuid1056; 1490; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 17)
      Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Buildings; France; Hats; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Rivers; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - Two men in coats and hats, with the Place de la Concorde and the Luxor obelisk in the background (linked ref1084). 7.7 x 10.4 cm, Undated; cuid1057; 1491; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Fountains; Paris, France; Place de la Concorde; Photographic Prints; Hats; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man in striped jacket, reclining on a lawn with a two story building behind him (same handwriting ref1084 and ref1090). 10.3 x 7.5 cm, 1926; cuid1058; 1492; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Egypt; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Sandhurst, Berkshire, UK; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man in a suit standing in front of the Luxor obelisk in the Place de la Concorde, Paris, France same man ref1086). 11.0 x 8.3 cm, Undated; cuid1059; 1493; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Place de la Concorde; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Men; Paris, France
    - Mansour Beih Series - Three men posing at the foot of some stairs. 6.8 x 11.2 cm, Undated; cuid1060; 1494; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; France; Egypt; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A view the Ponte Alexander III in Paris, France. 6.9 x 11.3 cm, Undated; cuid1061; 1495; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Paris, France; Bridges; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Buildings
    - Mansour Beih Series - A soldier standing in front of Sandhurst College (same handwriting as ref1084 and ref1086). 10.3 x 7.7 cm, March 1926; cuid1062; 1496; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; France; Buildings; Individual Portraits; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Egypt; Men; Sandhurst, Berkshire, UK; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - Four men and a woman with a white fur, standing in front of a house (linked ref1088 and ref1095). 11.3 x 6.8 cm, 1928; cuid1063; 1497; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 18)
      Fur Garments; Women; Men; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Egypt; Arabic Writing; Houses; Group Portraits; Buildings; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - A man standing in front of a fountain with some large buildings in the background.(same handwriting as ref1091). 6.8 x 11.3 cm, 6-1-1929; cuid1064; 1501; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Photographic Prints; Egypt; Hats; Men; Fountains; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Individual Portraits; Paris, France; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - Two men in suits sitting in a room with wallpaper. 6.3 x 8.4 cm, Undated; cuid1065; 1505; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)
      Men; Houses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
    - Mansour Beih Series - Two men in suits sitting in a cafe. Same man from ref1099. 5.2 x 8.0 cm, Undated; cuid1066; 1507; Unknown (Box 5, Folder 19)